<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IsKlinika</string>

    <string-array name="medication_status">
        <item>Currently Taking</item>
        <item>Completed</item>
        <item>From clinic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="add_medication_status">
        <item>Currently Taking</item>
        <item>Completed</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="charts">
        <item>BMI</item>
        <item>Height and Weight</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sort_by">
        <item>Latest</item>
        <item>Oldest</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="upload">
        <item>Medical Certificate</item>
        <item>Lab Result</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="illness">
        <item>Ongoing</item>
        <item>Recovered</item>
        <item>Chronic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_password">Are you sure you want to update your password</string>

    <string name="title">Do you want to delete the record?</string>
    <string name="supporting_text">Selecting remove will delete the record</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>

    <string-array name="allergies">
        <item>Drug</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Insect</item>
        <item>Latex</item>
        <item>Mold</item>
        <item>Pet</item>
        <item>Pollen</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="privacy">
        Last updated: May 29, 2022 \n \n
        Please read these terms and conditions carefully before using Our Service. \n \n

        <b><u>Table of Content</u></b> \n
        \n \t I. Interpretation and Definitions
        \n \t II. Acknowledgements
        \n \t III. "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" Disclaimer
        \n \t IV. Governing Law
        \n \t V. Disputes Resolution
        \n \t VI. Changes to These Terms and Conditions
        \n \t VII. Contact Us
        \n \n
        <b><u> I. Interpretation and Definitions</u></b> \n
        <b> I.a Interpretation</b>\n
        The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.
        \n \n

        <b> I.b Definitions</b>\n
        For the purposes of these Terms and Conditions: \n \n
            \t <b>Application</b> means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named IsKlinika
            \n \t <b>Country</b> refers to: Philippines
            \n \t <b>Company</b> (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to IsKlinika.
            \n \t <b>Device</b> means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.
            \n \t <b>Service</b> refers to the Application.
            \n \t <b>Terms and Conditions</b> (also referred as "Terms") mean these Terms and Conditions that form the entire agreement between You and the Company regarding the use of the Service. This Terms and Conditions agreement has been created with the help of the Terms and Conditions Generator.
            \n \t <b>You</b> means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
        \n \n
        <b><u>II. Acknowledgements</u></b> \n
            These are the Terms and Conditions governing the use of this Service and the agreement that operates between You and the Company. These Terms and Conditions set out the rights and obligations of all users regarding the use of the Service.
        \n \n Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on Your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.
        \n \n By accessing or using the Service You agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If You disagree with any part of these Terms and Conditions then You may not access the Service.
        \n \n You represent that you are over the age of 18. The Company does not permit those under 18 to use the Service.
        \n \n Your access to and use of the Service is also conditioned on Your acceptance of and compliance with the Privacy Policy of the Company. Our Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your personal information when You use the Application or the Website and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You. Please read Our Privacy Policy carefully before using Our Service.

        \n \n
        <b><u>III. "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" Disclaimer</u></b> \n
        The Service is provided to You "AS IS" and "AS AVAILABLE" and with all faults and defects without warranty of any kind. To the maximum extent permitted under applicable law, the Company, on its own behalf and on behalf of its Affiliates and its and their respective licensors and service providers, expressly disclaims all warranties, whether express, implied, statutory or otherwise, with respect to the Service, including all implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement, and warranties that may arise out of course of dealing, course of performance, usage or trade practice. Without limitation to the foregoing, the Company provides no warranty or undertaking, and makes no representation of any kind that the Service will meet Your requirements, achieve any intended results, be compatible or work with any other software, applications, systems or services, operate without interruption, meet any performance or reliability standards or be error free or that any errors or defects can or will be corrected.
        \n \n Without limiting the foregoing, neither the Company nor any of the company\'s provider makes any representation or warranty of any kind, express or implied: (i) as to the operation or availability of the Service, or the information, content, and materials or products included thereon; (ii) that the Service will be uninterrupted or error-free; (iii) as to the accuracy, reliability, or currency of any information or content provided through the Service; or (iv) that the Service, its servers, the content, or e-mails sent from or on behalf of the Company are free of viruses, scripts, trojan horses, worms, malware, timebombs or other harmful components.
        \n \n Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of certain types of warranties or limitations on applicable statutory rights of a consumer, so some or all of the above exclusions and limitations may not apply to You. But in such a case the exclusions and limitations set forth in this section shall be applied to the greatest extent enforceable under applicable law.

        \n \n
        <b><u>IV. Governing Law</u></b> \n
            The laws of the Country, excluding its conflicts of law rules, shall govern this Terms and Your use of the Service.
        \n \n
        <b><u>V. Disputes Resolution</u></b> \n
            If You have any concern or dispute about the Service, You agree to first try to resolve the dispute informally by contacting the Company.
        \n \n
        <b><u>VI. Changes to These Terms and Conditions</u></b> \n
        We reserve the right, at Our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material We will make reasonable efforts to provide at least 30 days\' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at Our sole discretion.
        \n  \n
        By continuing to access or use Our Service after those revisions become effective, You agree to be bound by the revised terms. If You do not agree to the new terms, in whole or in part, please stop using the website and the Service.\n

        \n
        <b><u>VII. Contact Us</u></b> \n
            If you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions, You can contact us: capstonegroup97@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string name="privacy_data">
        Last updated: May 29, 2022 \n \n
        Please read this privacy policy carefully before using Our Service. \n \n

        <b><u>Table of Content</u></b> \n
        \n \t I. Privacy Statement
        \n \t II. The Collection and Use of Personal Information
        \n \n \t \t IIa. What kind of information is collected?
        \n \t \t IIb. How it is collected?
        \n \t \t IIc. How it is managed and stored?
        \n \t \t IId. How it is used?
        \n \t \t IIe. How you can update and access information relating to you?
        \n \n
        <b><u> I. Privacy Statement</u></b> \n
        This PRIVACY STATEMENT sets out how <b>IsKlinika</b> uses personal information of the students in the clinic and explains the collection of personal information.
        \n \n
        The IsKlinika privacy policy applies to all information acquired from the clinic and parent users.
        \n \n
        Information collected and held by IsKlinika is subject to the <b>Data Privacy Act of 2012</b>, and IsKlinika respects and supports privacy protection in relation to information collected. IsKlinika is committed to comply with the <b>Data Privacy Act (Republic Act No. 10173).</b>
        \n \n
        \n
        <b><u> II. The Collection and Use of Personal Information</u></b> \n
        \n \t <b>IIa. What kind of information is collected?</b>
        \n \n \t <b>IsKlinika</b> collects and hold information relating to students personal and health-related information. This information includes name, address, gender, guardian information, and healthcare provider information.
        \n \n \t <b>IIb. How it is collected?</b>
        \n \n \t The collection of data happens whenever the student enrolls for the current school year. The school\'s IT department sets up the account for all the users. The school clinic collects the different personal information from the registrar and as well as the forms that parents fill-up during enrollment. Health-related information are collected from the student\'s visit in the clinic and the information added by the parent.
        \n \n \t <b>IIc. How it is managed and stored?</b>
        \n \n \t  All the collected information are stored in a cloud database and it is managed by the school\'s IT department.
        \n \n \t <b>IId. How it is used?</b>
        \n \n \t  IsKlinika uses the information contained in the database to allow the school clinic to come up with a better overall health understanding of the student patient. The school clinic also uses this as a guide on how they will provide immediate and preventive care to the students. The school clinic and IsKlinika ensures that all information are not used for any purposes outside the school setting.
        \n No persons other than the school clinic and the IT department are authorized to access any information stored in the cloud database. All person who can access the information are required to maintain its confidentiality and comply with privacy laws.
        \n \n \t <b>IIe. How you can update and access information relating to you?</b>
        \n \n \t The application allows the parent user to update their user information such as their name, email, and contact number. They are also allowed to update the personal information of their children that are currently enrolled in the school. Meanwhile, users are also allowed to update their passwords, and in situations that they have forgotten about their passwords they can easily change it through the "Forgot password".

    </string>
    <string name="emailSent">
        The code has been sent to your email.
    </string>
</resources>